#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ wolfgangweston (LinkedIn) www.realorganicseo.com (Company)

### Top Skills

Attention to Detail Voice over IP (VoIP) Transportation

## Languages

English
Spanish (Limited Working)

#### Certifications

Preventing Workplace Harassment Preventing Workplace Harassment

### Honors-Awards

Student Achievement Award Highest Honors Award Perfect Attendance Award

# Wolfgang Weston

Technology / SEM Specialist
Albuquerque, New Mexico, United States

# Summary

Since 1999 my work has involved web and tech in one facet or another... in particular SEO, or Search Engine Optimization. Analyzed the project site, its competitors and implemented necessary changes to the site. The work involves hard coding and programming on the site (HTML) and tracking of performance with reports for high visibility on search engines.

I have also performed design, architecture, construction, upgrade and maintenance of PC and Laptop systems for home and offices and clients. I have been a project technician, responsible for the project management and installation of Hospital/Clinical printers and user stations.

Also involved with the trade: LAN Design and Installation - Preparation and splicing of CAT5/6 data cables and installation of appropriate connectors; Splicing, crimping and installation; Wireless Network Installation – WAN setup, maintenance and repair, includes VoIP installation for telephone systems.

Experience: Adobe Acrobat, Photoshop & Premiere, cabling, computer hardware, copy-writing, CSS, digital video, MS Frontpage, HTML, industry analysis, internet marketing, Java, LAN, Excel, Outlook, Word, Powerpoint, network installation, PC design, hardware, peripherals, search engine optimization (SEO), troubleshooting, video editing, video production, VoIP, Web Development.

# Experience

Uber ATG
Development Vehicle Operator
September 2016 - July 2018 (1 year 11 months)
Greater Pittsburgh Area

Vehicle Operator - Self Driving

- Vehicle Operator with self-driving technology. Passenger Operations and Beta Test Driver in Ford Fusion and Volvo XC-90 vehicle platforms.
- Expertly trained in high-speed scenarios for safety and precision. Working with the latest format of vehicular automation.
- Picking up and taking customers and VIP riders to their destinations throughout the mapped Pittsburgh, PA area.
- Assisted Trainers with Trainees (Mentoring) in practical, safe street and passenger operations (self-driving).

#### Amazon

Fulfillment Specialist January 2016 - August 2016 (8 months)

Scanning packages, organizing pallets for shipments bound to regional post offices.

#### Wolfline Productions

Computer Design, Maintenance, Upgrade and Repair Specialist October 1999 - September 2012 (13 years)

- Designed, constructed, upgraded and maintained PC and Laptop systems and architecture for home and office for home businesses and consumers.
- Engineered networking and wireless systems. Installed all OS, hardware, software, peripherals and systems security.
- This job is self-employment.

# The Kemtah Group, Inc.

Special Projects Technician (Presbyterian Hospital) July 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 1 month)

- Maintained PC and Laptop systems, printers and scanning devices for medical environment, much of which was a break/fix scenario.
- Installed all OS, hardware, software, peripherals and systems security directly and remotely.
- Worked directly with PresRecord II Analysts to deploy EMR upgrade label printers used with Epic and FormFast.
- Adept in creating Service Requests in CA with accuracy, legibility and precise information to the specific needs of the project.

Veritude (Fidelity Investments Inc.)
Health and Insurance Benefits Associate
September 2010 - January 2011 (5 months)

- Assisted with customers with their health insurance, life insurance, dependents care, Health Savings Accounts, Health Flexible Spending Accounts, and Annual Enrollments and Online Navigation.
- Described to customers the differences between various health and welfare programs provided by their employers. Customer employers included IBM, Merck, ABB, Texas Instruments and BaSF.

### RealOrganicSEO.com

Owner/President and (SEO) Search Engine Optimization Specialist April 2001 - August 2010 (9 years 5 months)

San Diego, Phoenix, Albuquerque

- Surveyed and created specific SEO enhancements to allow for highly visible organic search engine placement, utilizing industry research for search engine strategy, copy-writing, building and managing keyword lists.
- Expertly coded raw HTML with Notepad and use of web editors like FrontPage.
- Maintained Pay-Per-Click and SEM campaign experience, managed CPC accounts with Google, Yahoo and MSN.

#### Z57

Website Production Specialist August 2009 - February 2010 (7 months)

- Work with clients to build initial real estate related web product.
- Determine specific client needs and contact information.
- Assist clients with implementation of design and marketing strategy that conforms to client specific parameters and customization.

#### Citibank Call Center

Collections/Customer Service
December 2007 - August 2009 (1 year 9 months)

- All encompassing handling of customer service related issues for inbound telephone inquiries, direct communication and constant feedback in a team-environment with statistical goal orientation and active corporate culture.
- Consistently achieved higher than expected goals in all required statistical categories.

TalkShowThis.com
Producer, Floor Director
October 2006 - March 2007 (6 months)

- Produced and directed live, in-studio talk show for both television and online audience.
- Edited all pre-production and post-production video content, each episode for online viewing and converted show content to web friendly video formats.
- Maintained social media promotion and advertising.

Homes.com

New Account Sales Specialist September 2001 - February 2003 (1 year 6 months)

- Contacted potential clients for Real Estate Agent Web Sites and Enhancement Services.
- Outbound cold-called to qualified real estate professionals in need of a web based internet marketing platform.

Victoria Station

Waiter

1983 - 1985 (2 years)

Served food and drinks at a popular national chain of prime rib restaurants, this one located in San Diego, CA.

# Education

**ITT Technical Institute** 

Associates of Science, Computer Networking Systems · (2009 - 2011)

San Diego City College

Radio and Television · (1983 - 1985)

Patrick Henry High School

Diploma, General Education · (1979 - 1981)